kickerstart.com 2014-07-14

# Privacy Policy

Privacy 

SmartDeviceShow dearly respects your privacy and is committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at SmartDeviceShow.com The following discloses how we go about gather and disseminate information for this site. 

RSS Feeds and Email Updates 

If a user wishes to subscribe to the RSS Feeds or Email Updates, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. Absolutely never. 

Log Files and Stats 

Like most blogging platforms we use web-based analytics, in this case Google Analytics. This stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, tracks user’s movement in the whole, and gathers broad demographic information for aggregate use. (Note: IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.) 

Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site doesn’t use cookies. However, some of our business partners use cookies on this site (for example – advertisers). We can’t access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them, the same type of information logged in the stats is often gathered via cookies. 

Links 

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We suggest users be aware of this when they leave SmartDeviceShow and read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by SolidSmack. 

Advertisers 

Ad are delivered through our internal advertising system. However, occasionally, we use outside ad companies to display ads on this blog. These ads may contain cookies used by the advertising companies. We do not have access to this information. SmartDeviceShow occasionally display ads from the following advertising companies: Google Adsense. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies. 

Contact Information 

If you have any questions or concerns please contact us at kickersmart#gmail.com
